// Export the quizData outside the component as a named export
export const quizData = [
    {
        question: "2 , 3 , 5 , 7 , 11 , ?",
        answer: "13",
        options: ["23", "14", "41", "13"],
    },
    {
        question: "7 , 21 , 42 , 126 , 252 , ?",
        answer: "756",
        options: ["210", "733", "756", "84"],
    },
    {
        question: "Choose The One Which Is Different From Rest",
        answer: "Sharp",
        options: ["Tall", "Huge", "Thin", "Sharp"],
    },
    {
        question: "If remain = 396715, then airmen = ?",
        answer: "713695",
        options: ["169753", "563791", "971365", "713695"],
    },
    {
        question: "REASON : SFBTPO :: THINK : ?",
        answer: "UIJOL",
        options: ["SGHMJ", "UIJOL", "UHNKI", "UJKPM"],
    },
    {
        question: "Choose The One Which Is Different From Rest",
        answer: "Pink",
        options: ["Orange", "Indigo", "Yellow", "Pink"],
    },
    {
        question: "B, D, F, I, L, P , ?",
        answer: "T",
        options: ["A", "L", "T", "W"],
    },
    {
        question: "13, 35, 57, 79, 911 , ?",
        answer: "1113",
        options: ["1110", "1112", "1113", "1315"],
    },
    {
        question: "If secured = 1834985, then rescued = ?",
        answer: "9813485",
        options: ["9813762", "9813485", "3498185", "1348598"],
    },
    {
        question: "Z, U, Q , ?, L",
        answer: "N",
        options: ["G", "B", "Z", "N"],
    },
    
];

